<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>seisokeii blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link>
        <description>seisokeii&#39;s blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Noway@bimbimbambam (seisokeii)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Noway@bimbimbambam (seisokeii)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:39:33 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Open Network Install Environment (ONIE) Simple Introduction</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/onie/onie-intro/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:39:33 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>seisokeii</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/onie/onie-intro/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<hr>
<p>If you have ever used a whitebox switch, you maybe know what Open Network Install Environment is ~
Here is a simple brief introduction to ONIE. The first task during my internship at Edge-core Networks was to make a new device compatible with ONIE, which means making ONIE run on the new device.</p>
<h2 id="what-is-onie">What is ONIE?</h2>
<p>In short, ONIE is a lightweight Linux environment that makes it easy to install Network Operating System (NOS).</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>ACS Custom Noise Cancelling Earplugs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/earplug/acs-earplug01/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 16:28:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>seisokeii</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/earplug/acs-earplug01/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>I decided to share my experience since there aren&rsquo;t many people talking about this on internet.</p>
<p>So why did I want custom earplugs? Mainly because my friends often invite me to hardstyle nightclubs and music festivals like Defqon.1, Intents, etc., and eardrums are very fragile. I don&rsquo;t want to lose my hearing so early QQ</p>
<p>But there&rsquo;s another reason, which might be the bigger one, that sometimes I need to work on equipment in the network room or server room, and sometimes I stay there for a long time, and the high-frequency fans are super noisy&hellip; For these reasons, I wanted to find a way to protect my ears.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Halo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/halo/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:20:52 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>seisokeii</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/halo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>The first post is dedicated to Hugo!</p>
<p>First of all, I have to say that my luck is really terrible&hellip; I read many articles on the Internet that said Hugo can be set up in 5 minutes, but it took me a day (more than 20 hours) to get it done before I started writing this post&hellip;</p>
<p>As for the reason&hellip; I chose a cool theme to use at the beginning, but almost every theme only mentioned the git submodule installation and then ended. The rest is up to you to figure out. For those who understand, this is true. But for a super newbie like me, it&rsquo;s hard to say, especially for those who don&rsquo;t read the documentation, which is where I struggled.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
