<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SONiC - Tag - seisokeii blog</title>
        <link>https://seisokeii.github.io/en/tags/sonic/</link>
        <description>SONiC - Tag - seisokeii blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Noway@bimbimbambam (seisokeii)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Noway@bimbimbambam (seisokeii)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:03:33 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seisokeii.github.io/en/tags/sonic/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Open Network Install Environment (ONIE) How to build?</title>
    <link>https://seisokeii.github.io/en/posts/onie/onie-build/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:03:33 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>seisokeii</author>
    <guid>https://seisokeii.github.io/en/posts/onie/onie-build/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<hr>
<p>Following the previous article <code>ONIE Simple Introduction</code>, let&rsquo;s briefly share how ONIE is built!</p>
<p>This will be similar to a tutorial, but of course it&rsquo;s impossible to put company information here~ It&rsquo;s just a general
look at how a network equipment manufacturer makes this thing.</p>
<h2 id="preparation---prepare-the-development-environment">Preparation - Prepare the development environment</h2>
<p>Honestly, the development environment is just a standard Linux machine, I use a virtual machine~</p>
<p>This environment is actually based on the recommendations on the ONIE official website to install the DUE package made
by
CumulusNetworks, otherwise anyone who has compiled the Linux Kernel should know how dog shit the dependency is. After
using DUE, everything will be automatically handled~</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Open Network Install Environment (ONIE) Simple Introduction</title>
    <link>https://seisokeii.github.io/en/posts/onie/onie-intro/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:39:33 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>seisokeii</author>
    <guid>https://seisokeii.github.io/en/posts/onie/onie-intro/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<hr>
<p>If you have ever used a whitebox switch, you maybe know what Open Network Install Environment is ~
Here is a simple brief introduction to ONIE. The first task during my internship at Edge-core Networks was to make a new
device compatible with ONIE, which means making ONIE run on the new device.</p>
<h2 id="what-is-onie">What is ONIE?</h2>
<p>In short, ONIE is a lightweight Linux environment that makes it easy to install Network Operating System (NOS).</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
